Ajay Ko Hello
Hello Friends Welcome Back To Your Channel
Wealth Was Friends Today We Are Going To Talk About
Private Insurance Sector
Companies Tricks Number One
According To Market HDFC Life Number Two
SBI Life Number Three ICICI
Prudential In Numbers ICICI Lombard
Upcoming Result Posting Company's
Edward Has Recently Declared Its Result The
Company Is In Profit Business Model
You Can See Insurance Company's
Subscribe To Know What You Should Do
Hello Friends Don't Forget To Like Share
And Subscribe Do Press The Bell Icon So
That You Keep Getting Our Latest
Videos Till Now
First Keyword In All Business Model Of
Insurance Company Insurance company's work is to
make a plan, make the plan
reach the people and collect its premium from the people
When a claim comes then that claim has to be
settled Stand
A Premium Collection Is An Example Take a
hundred rupees then claim settlement and
average profit is 70% in which you are
marketing, even if you eliminate Bigg Boss you will still earn at
least 6 to 65  The
company has 90% staff and it makes a profit.
I am very active during school plans,
sometimes they are less active, but only on a
bridge. The company has a margin of 50% on street offices and
profits. Now how do companies earn
from the premium? The correct answer is well, the
investment they have made is
that the insurance
company invests money. The insurance company
invests in government securities. 90%
of the money is in something like shares and securities of the
government. In such a place where we
know that there is no money, neither did it happen.
Now let us look at the market cap of these four companies. HDFC Life,
SBI Life, ICICI Prudential,
ICICI Lombard.
One thing to see is
that the ranking in this set is numbered by money,
and yet its
current market price of CMP is the highest, although the
other three are much below it. Why is this so? All
three companies have about 20%
promoter holding. So, this is really very good. The promoter
holding of all four companies is above 50%, so that is
very good. We show you that the market cap of
ICICI  Lombard is more expensive
20 is another company, so for that,
HDFC Life of CCEA, SBI Life, ICICI
Prudential, these three insurance companies are
market leaders but all three of them
work in only one segment,
inverter 208, temple run, two
old creams, graduation, maritime, you will
get money, helpline means cancer related,
combination related, whatever
new all the recently launched cardiac, if
you have any problem with height, then
people will pay money for that, retirement
is launched, savings and investment plan, Dheeraj
Yadav, wedding of HDFC Life, lucky
wealth creation, what is the meaning of SBA, a
bit more or less, those dealers in smart,
please subscribe, money plant, you
can see that the market cap of the company providing this thing is
required, but now we will see
from this number, disturbance, disturbance, return in 15 days,
profit of any company, home insurance
scam
kilometers, if anyone knows that
if there are more earthquakes in Delhi,
then  If someone comes there to
buy a policy, then his premium will be
much higher than the person staying in
Mumbai because Mumbai did not have any
great records of the earth. So in that
case, this company also has to know where
problems can arise. How much premium should we charge here?
Motor Insurance, two
wheeler car, single donor, multiple vehicle. This is a very
good thing which adds up only in
ICICI Lombard Marine Insurance. It is
not because you have transported goods that there is
some problem or not, then
that is to be seen. I mean, canteen
insurance, if the shipment has left from here and
reached here, no claim, which gives the company a
straight away profit and one
and maximum paisa at any place, they have more fibers.
And we only side, any business owner
or any person takes suicide insurance,
whether he is coming in these directions, we know that we are going into complete bankruptcy in the
last month itself,
but there is peace of mind. Celery,
if something happens then the company will  Spoil 800 cases
everywhere tips five percent means service and
company is also going to have a problem with maximum five of its top funders in the case
Saudi Arabia has mentally prepared that we will have to
settle five claims Health
insurance this is very important Singh will
talk about it in the last
how much growth has happened due to connected options
Business insurance of these groups coming in
bulk for workers for fire
This is ICICI Lombard provides
anti corruption so that if you are somewhere out of India then
your
house can be insured for all this ICICI
Lombard provides crop insurance This is the state
of the art thing only
ICICI Lombard provides at many petrol
stations you can see that their guys
sit with a small barricade
in the corner where they
sit with a big Amarela, it used to be written on it
such number two wheeler
insurance Infibeam Inch so all such things
they promote a lot  And this
company is really good, now the important thing is to
see my 41 inch, but I am not you, the
insurance option for tomorrow, the RTO
means the government has made it mandatory that you have to
wait for tomorrow, but I am not, so
people know that just like tomorrow's
insurance, they also do their own
insurance together, now people have made it, so for that, if you don't have
money to do
management studies of login, which
explains how will you do in 2nd odi
retirement like this, it is very important this
that Aishwarya is here, I am not your
retirement plan, I have my own plans
vs right time for you to make your
retirement nest, and as soon as I tell you this thing, the
education system buried in people's mind, people are
looking forward for such a
clan game, turn on what can happen in tomorrow, the
risk is so much, so
see what is the strong point,
first of all, you get income tax deduction on
taking mediclaim, that is,
on taking health insurance, under section
From 2500 to fifty thousand depending on the
senior citizen and everything vehicle motor
insurance class third party
insurance you have to take
how much RTO norms clean it is in two wheeler
you also know that a lot of Jubilee came from
us but this company knows that this
company has to take insurance so these
companies keep on growing in less than five per cent of
total population in
India which even aware about the insurance
suit with moral education as well as
government promotions but now
in this diction and TV commercials
insurance is coming into limelight at only five per cent people
are * all illnesses payer *
insurance people know that one should
take insurance so in these cases
not yet more than five percent the
entire market is open
that now let's talk about important then
figures on these numbers profit of
today if you had invested money in all these companies i.e.
HDFC Life in 2019 then only
company vs  Pet Me Company
Episode 660 CMP So you should ignore this column
that if you had deposited 1 lakh rupees a
year ago on the same date then you would have got 1 lakh 25
thousand rupees so in the benefit of 25 percent
you
get maximum 4% that is 108000 of 1 lakh here
125000 of 1 lakh so let's see safe and secure dance
balance Mumbai that SBI Life would have given
you 50% return in A production 70% and
ICICI Lombard 22% return,
we see that these three
companies 12 n3 and you got listed in 2017, till now
they have
returned 90% of your money in 3 years i.e. 1
lakh has become 1 lakh 20 thousand 800
very good things and a product service
from 2016 so if someone
kept the money folded in it for 3 years for 4 years then also 42%
You have got a return of
A plus debit the company by things that is very
good thing election what do you hold and right
now the result of 2014 is of three company so
we should first focus on that,
straight away from the tweet you put ₹500
in medical maximum time benefit you don't thing should be
big, you do not do it
completely subscribe in front of that then you
invest and 1000 definitely result you will get the
entire money of mediclaim,
you can do ICICI Prudential Life Insurance, we have
made a life video of Brett Lee Third of July, you
can see its link in the description, only then
that company is 1000 company,
more than 600 the three do subscribe button, this
insurance company has given, so if you
subscribe to this video channel one to three
minimum then take it, then you can
get good returns, do
not forget to subscribe to Meghnad and very soon
we will bring a new video with such an interesting
thank you in which you will know that the
profit margin is very high and  Your
money can get multibagger returns.
Please do tell us by commenting which company
's sales you would like to take. Thank you. It was a great experience.